RG 142, General Federation of Women's Clubs of Connecticut
Connecticut State Library
- Series 4. Centennial, 1995-1998
  - T001355
    - President's reports, 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Programs, 1966 February 23-1972 May 4 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Promise summit, 1997 January 12-1998 July 6 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Public relations, 1995 July 19-1997 August 19 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Read 3 Connecticut, 1997 August 20-1998 November 18 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Reporting workshops, 1996 September 18-1997 January 21 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Safe roads coalition, 1997 September 16-1998 May 11 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Save outdoor sculpture, 1997 October 6-1998 January 31 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Special Olympics, 1996 November 7-1997 September 29 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Tea pot play, 1996 September 13-1996 November 10 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Veterans, 1997 April 13-1997 October 25 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Very Special Arts Connecticut, 1996 July 10-1998 February 27 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Wesleyan, 1996 August 3-1997 July 2 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Women in Military Service for America, 1997 June 7-1997 October 17 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Women's Hall of Fame, 1996 September 26-1997 September 12 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Publications, 1996 May 13 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Annual report to General Federation of Women's Clubs, International, 1997 March 31 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Annual report to General Federation of Women's Clubs, International, 1998 April 1 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Minutes, centennial administration, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Minutes, centennial administration, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Series 5. Photographs, 1976
  - T001355
    - Home energy check slide show, 1976; 1 box of photographic slides (Box 1)
- Series 6. Artifacts, 1897-2011
  - T001355
    - Artifacts, 1897-1930; Contains a delegate's badge, a medal, a guestbook, and a stamp of a woman's likeness, most likely of Florence Sutton. (Box 1)
  - 2013-024
    - Artifacts, 2010-2011; Contains a lapel button and a plaque. (Box 1)
- Series 7. Sound Recordings, 1953-1963
  - T001355 (Box Shared audio disc box)
    - Panel of state presidents, parts 1 and 2, 1953; 1 vinyl record; This item is separated from the records. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
    - Panel of state presidents, parts 3 and 4, 1953; 1 vinyl record; This item is separated from the records. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
    - The Preservation of Our American Heritage, parts 1 and 2, 1953; 1 vinyl record; This item is separated from the records. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
    - The Preservation of Our American Heritage, parts 3 and 4, 1953; 1 vinyl record; This item is separated from the records. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
    - What Next America? parts 1 and 2, 1954; 1 vinyl record; This item is separated from the records. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
    - What Next America? parts 3 and 4, 1954; 1 vinyl record; This item is separated from the records. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
    - Woman to World, parts 1 and 4, 1963; 1 vinyl record; This item is separated from the records. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
    - Woman to World, parts 2 and 3, 1963; 1 vinyl record; This item is separated from the records. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
    - Strengthen the Arm of Liberty, 1963; 2 vinyl records; This item is separated from the records. Contact State Archives staff for assistance..
    - Strengthen the Arm of Liberty, 1963; sheet music
    - Tables of contents of sound recordings, 1963; Contains information on sound recordings from 62nd and 63rd national annual conventions. (Box 32)
- Series 8. Videos, circa 2009-2010
  - T001355
    - Vets OASIS, Channel 23, Danbury, circa 2010; 1 DVD, 18 min., 51 sec.; This item is separated from the records. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
      A panel discussion of the GFWCT Vets OASIS state project which includes the following General Federation of Women Clubs CT members: Gloria Hutchinson, co-chair of Vets OASIS; Kathy Aiello, co-chair Vets OASIS project; Grace Matyskiela, Past GFWCT Past President (2008-2010); and Sheila Vetter(?), GFWCT District 1.
  - 2016-009
    - Vets OASIS, Channel 23, Danbury, circa 2010; 1 DVD, 18 min., 51 sec.; This item is separated from the records. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
    - American Mural Project, Winsted, 2009; 1 DVD, 7 min., 13 sec.; This item is separated from the records. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
      The video features Ellen Griesedieck, Artist and Founder American Mural Project, talking about the project which is a tribute to work.
- Series 9. Removable Media, 2008-2010
  - 2016-009
    - GFWC/CT administrative minutes, bullets, and convention planning, 2008-2010; 1 compact disc 37 Microsoft Word documents, 65.5 MB; This item is separated from the records. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.